Double peach from the left
双桃从左起
Determined to work in a commercial bank for analysis
立志到商业银行工作进行分析
Could it be that she also wants to sneak into the business?
难道她也想混进这行生意？
but my existence
但我的存在
The biggest threat to her
对她最大的威胁
Zuo Shuangtao wants to kill you
左双涛想杀了你
It’s not that Zuo Shuangtao wants to kill me
左双涛不是想杀我
If she wants to kill me
如果她想杀我
Then she has too many opportunities
那么她的机会太多了
Why do you want to do it in a movie theater?
为什么要在电影院看？
And the most important thing
最重要的是
What
什么
intuition
直觉
I trust my intuition
我相信我的直觉
It must not be Zuo Shuangtao who wants to kill me
想杀我的一定不是左双涛
I know your feelings for Zuo Shuangtao
我知道你对左双涛的感情
But you can't do it because of feelings
但你不能因为感情而这么做
and affect one's own judgment
并影响自己的判断
old road
老路
I trust my judgment
我相信我的判断
You are in a very dangerous situation now
你现在的处境非常危险
The organization is re-investigating Zuo Shuangtao’s background
组织正在重新调查左双涛的背景
No result yet
还没有结果
Once verified
一旦核实
She belongs to the organization
她属于该组织
You must evacuate Taihe Trading Company immediately
你必须立即撤离泰和商贸公司
Evacuate
撤离
How can this be done?
如何才能做到这一点？
Now the Shan plan has just begun to take shape.
现在掸邦的计划才刚刚开始成形。
And this negotiation incident
而这次谈判事件
What kind of secret is hidden behind it?
这背后究竟隐藏着怎样的秘密？
foggy
有雾
There is still a long way to go
还有很长的路要走
How can I evacuate at this time?
这个时候我该如何疏散呢？
Do not evacuate
不要疏散
How to ensure the safety of your identity
如何确保您的身份安全
Even if Zuo Shuangtao knows my identity
就算左双涛知道我的身份
She will definitely not betray me
她绝对不会背叛我
It's not just your personal safety
这不仅仅是您的人身安全
And the security of intelligence
以及情报的安全
And the security of the organization
以及组织的安全
How can you guarantee the information you got?
你如何保证你得到的信息？
Will not be discovered by Zuo Shuangtao
不会被左双涛发现
If this information falls into
如果此信息属于
In the hands of the organization behind her
在她背后的组织手中
how can you guarantee
你怎么保证
There will be no disadvantageous situation for us
不会出现对我们不利的情况
besides
除了
What organization does Zuo Shuangtao belong to?
左双涛属于什么组织？
Don't know yet
还不知道
military tongzhongtong
军事同中通
Civilian anti-Japanese anti-corruption groups are possible
民间抗日反腐团体是可能的
these organizations and enemies
这些组织和敌人
have a very complicated relationship
关系非常复杂
inside them
在他们里面
There are a lot of vacillating double-dealers
有很多犹豫不决的两面派
Juntong Xiang No. 76
Juntong Xiang No. 76
How many of their own people were betrayed?
有多少自己的人被出卖了？
You should know
你应该知道
Even if Zuo Shuangtao doesn’t betray you
就算左双涛不背叛你
But what about her organization?
但她的组织呢？
My old ways
我的老方法
And the most important thing
最重要的是
This is an order
这是一个订单
yes
是的
Mrs. Chen
陈女士
Why didn't you come with Section Chief Chen?
你怎么没跟陈科长一起来？
Newcomer
新人
Just came to work
刚来上班
Of course you have to come earlier
当然你得早点来
unlike him
不像他
Old fried dough sticks
老油条
you
你
You come to work
你来上班
Is Manager Luo here?
罗经理在吗？
I'm coming
我来了
OK
好的
I'll go find him
我去找他
work
工作
come here
过来
Manager Luo
Manager Luo
manager
经理
Fangfang
Fangfang
starting today
从今天开始
You don't have to work so hard
你不必那么努力工作
One person holds two jobs
一个人身兼两职
You just have to be responsible
你只需要负责
Administrator of archives
档案管理员
That's it
就是这样
What
什么
from now on
今后
Accountant in Finance Office
财务室会计
Ms. Zuo will be in charge.
左女士将负责。
no
不
why
为什么
She studied finance in college
她在大学学的是金融
Our unit also lacks an accountant
我们单位还缺会计
This is called
这就是所谓的
Born at the right time
出生在正确的时间
Apply what you learned
应用你所学到的知识
I disagree
我不同意
You never asked her to be an accountant before
你以前从未要求她成为一名会计师
It seems I don’t need your consent for this, right?
看来我不需要你的同意，对吗？
I said Luo Guanqun
I said Luo Guanqun
I did a good job
我做得很好
Why should I let her take my place?
我为什么要让她取代我的位置？
Yes, Manager Luo
是的，罗经理
Didn't you say that before?
你之前不是说过吗？
Do you want me to work with Sister Fangfang?
要我和芳芳姐一起工作吗？
Why did I end up taking her place?
为什么我最终取代了她的位置？
What are you pretending to be?
你在假装什么？
I think it's you
我想是你
With your uncle Yu Shanren’s power,
以你舅舅余山人的势力，
Put pressure on Manager Luo
给罗经理施压
I can
我可以
That's right
这是正确的
I'm here to replace you
我是来代替你的
Not convinced?
不相信？
Okay, okay, okay
好吧好吧好吧
You see, we haven’t done anything together yet.
你看，我们还没有一起做过任何事。
That's all
就这样
Can I let you work together?
我可以让你一起工作吗？
Before you get off work
下班之前
You must finish handing over this matter.
你必须把这件事交出去。
This Captain Zhao
这位赵队长
Why have you become a polished commander recently?
为什么你最近变成了一名光鲜亮丽的指挥官？
There is no trace of Erduidao and Feng Qi either.
二对刀和风起也没有踪影。
Feng Qi seems to have gone on some secret mission.
风起似乎是去执行什么秘密任务了。
The two knives also went out.
两把刀也出去了。
Don't know where to go
不知道该去哪里
Just came back
刚回来
Qian Xiucai
Qian Xiucai
Don’t you usually just hold your copy?
你通常不只拿着你的副本吗？
Annals of the Eastern Zhou Dynasties?
东周纪年？
How to track the people in the business?
如何追踪企业中的人员？
So clear
十分清晰
This small business
这家小企业
Isn't it just a chronicle of the countries of the Eastern Zhou Dynasty?
不就是东周诸国的编年史吗？
Didn't you think of it?
你没想到吗？
I can still sit here and eat
我还可以坐在这里吃饭
I don’t understand what Captain Zhao is saying
听不懂赵队长在说什么
I know you are afraid
我知道你害怕
It doesn't matter
没关系
I just want to tell you
我只想告诉你
I'm Zhao An
我是赵安
It won't fall that easily
不会那么容易掉下来
sister-in-law
嫂子
Mrs. Luo Mrs. Luo
罗女士 罗女士
Then you eat first
那你先吃饭
I go first
我先走
Where is our business?
我们的生意在哪里？
The food in the cafeteria used to be quite delicious.
以前食堂的饭菜还是蛮好吃的。
But since Lao Luo’s relatives took over the contract
但自从老罗的亲戚接手了合同
Not as good as before
不如以前好
so
所以
The kind of person who relies on his own backer
那种靠自己靠山的人
A person who takes away someone else's position
抢夺别人职位的人
The worst thing
最坏的事
Who are you talking about?
你在说谁？
Those who criticize mulberry trees and huai trees
那些骂桑树、槐树的人
Please explain it clearly to me
请给我解释清楚
good
好的
I'm talking about you
我正在谈论你
Your grades in finance majoring in college
您大学金融专业的成绩
Can I not know?
我可以不知道吗？
Even if you write cheat sheets for the exam, you will fail.
即使你为考试写了备忘单，你也会失败。
Why do you replace Lu Fangfang?
为什么要取代卢芳芳呢？
He used to be in charge of concession affairs
他曾负责特许经营事务
So just follow the clue of cold dew
所以只要顺着寒露的线索
Check below
检查下面
Section Chief Chen
陈科长
Why don't you eat well?
为什么不好好吃饭呢？
Let’s play at a different table
让我们在不同的牌桌上玩吧
Captain Zhao
Captain Zhao
Do you want a piece of advice from me?
你需要我给你一些建议吗？
Advice
建议
My advice is
我的建议是
Never trust a woman before marriage
婚前永远不要相信女人
Before getting married, everything was coquettish.
结婚之前，一切都是风骚的。
Everything you do after you get married is wild.
结婚后你所做的一切都是疯狂的。
Section Chief Chen
陈科长
do not worry
不用担心
Our Captain Zhao doesn’t look for women before marriage.
我们赵队长婚前不找女人。
Shut up
住口
Who do you think is acting wild?
你认为谁表现得狂野？
Captain Zhao and I are chatting here.
我和赵队长正在这里聊天。
What are you interrupting?
你打扰什么？
Besides, did I talk about you?
另外，我有说到你吗？
Captain Zhao, eat slowly
赵队长，慢点吃
I am leaving
我走了
Don't go
别走
Why don't I go?
我为什么不去？
It's not clear yet
目前还不清楚
Don't follow me to annoy you
别跟着我来惹恼你
I will follow you
我会跟随你
cold dew
冷露
What are Erduidao going on this business trip to investigate?
二对刀这次出差是要调查什么？
How could Hanlu be involved?
韩璐怎么可能参与其中？
Double peach, I'm leaving first
双桃，我先走了
See you tomorrow
明天见
Miss Zuo
Miss Zuo
Nice to be your colleague
很高兴成为你的同事
I was new
我是新来的
Please take care of me in the future
今后请多多关照
are you looking for me
你在找我吗
It is said that
据说
You and Chen Jiaping had a fight
你和陈家平吵架了
how
如何
Couple quarreling
夫妻吵架
Is it abnormal?
是否异常？
Miss Zuo
Miss Zuo
actually
实际上
Why don't you get off work so late?
这么晚你怎么还不下班？
Miss Zuo
Miss Zuo
In fact, my love for you
其实我对你的爱
Never changed
从未改变过
Are you not sick?
你没病吧？
Although
虽然
you are married
你结婚了
But it does not matter
但是这没关系
We can still start over
我们仍然可以重新开始
Do you think that's possible
你认为这可能吗
here with me
在这陪着我
Nothing is impossible
没有什么是不可能的
You two wait a moment
你们两个稍等一下
What are you two doing?
你们两个在做什么？
we have something urgent
我们有紧急事
Wait a moment, wait a moment, wait a moment
等一下，等一下，等一下
What are you running for?
你跑来干嘛？
Not sir
不是先生
do we have any questions
我们有什么问题吗
no problem
没问题
I'm on patrol
我在巡逻
passing by here
路过这里
I want to remind you two gentlemen
我想提醒两位先生
Stop running around the French Concession in the middle of the night.
别再半夜在法租界跑来跑去了。
So as not to scare other citizens
以免吓到其他市民
The French Concession is so unsafe now.
现在法租界太不安全了。
The French Concession is quite safe.
法租界还是很安全的。
But I think you two
但我认为你们两个
Not very safe
不太安全
Please come back
请回来
Do you know these two people?
你认识这两个人吗？
I know you so well
我很了解你
Colleagues from my firm
我公司的同事
One is named Feng Qi
一个叫冯琪
One is called Chen Shugan
一个叫陈树干
They are all Zhao An's men
都是赵安的手下
What's the next task?
下一个任务是什么？
Walk
走
Chen Jiaping
Chen Jiaping
Rob a bank and steal documents
抢劫银行并窃取文件
You said it was anti-Japanese, I believed it
你说抗日我信了
What kind of anti-Japanese approach is following female celebrities?
追随女明星是一种什么样的反日做法？
Last time Feng Qi wanted to assassinate
上次风起想要刺杀
Japanese representatives participating in secret peace talks
日本代表参加秘密和谈
Now he is following Han Lu again
现在他又跟着韩露了
Could it be that the cold dew is also related to this secret peace talk?
难道寒露也和这次秘密和谈有关吗？
came back
回来
How did you come
你怎么来的
let me see you
让我看看你
sit down
坐下
What do you want to see me for?
你要见我做什么？
I'm coming this time
这次我来了
I want your forgiveness
我想要你的原谅
never mind
没关系
Now I don't think it's important
现在我认为这不重要
Besides, in your life
除此之外，在你的生活中
Love is just a condiment
爱情只是一种调味品
Climb up as an official
爬上做官
That's your main course
这是你的主菜
did not expect
没想到
so many years
这么多年
You still haven't changed
你还是没变
say
说
Still so cunning
还是那么狡猾
So what do you want me to say?
那么你想让我说什么？
You promised to love me forever
你答应过我会永远爱我
But once you have the position of director
但一旦你坐上了导演的位置
You can leave me who is sick
你可以离开我这个生病的人
Ran from Shanghai to Nanjing overnight
连夜从上海跑到南京
Listen to me and explain to you
听我给你解释一下
I'm tired
我累了
If you have nothing to do
如果你无事可做
I want to take a bath and rest
我想洗澡休息
I want to ask you a favor
我想请你帮个忙
What help?
有什么帮助？
Rent a house for me
给我租个房子
Why are you looking for me?
你为什么找我？
because of you
因为有你
in my life
在我生命中
most trusted person
最信任的人
do you know
你知道吗
every time I
每次我
Thinking of our previous moments
想起我们以前的时光
I will feel
我会感觉
that was my life
这就是我的生活
happiest
最幸福的
happiest moment
最幸福的时刻
Tomorrow at nine o'clock
明天九点
I'll call you on time
我会准时给你打电话
Are we fighting against Japan now?
现在我们正在和日本作战吗？
Still working as a tabloid reporter?
还在做小报记者吗？
There are too many people coming in and out here, right?
这里进出的人太多了吧？
see it
看见
that person
那个人
Came from Hanlu's house
从韩璐家来的
How did you come
你怎么来的
Miss Hanlu
韩璐小姐
I'm very sorry
我很抱歉
Coming to the door so unexpectedly
如此意外地找上门来
but
但
for your safety
为了你的安全
I hope you can answer my question
我希望你能回答我的问题
Do you have a very important friend?
你有一个非常重要的朋友吗？
I came to see you
我来看你了
No
不
After returning from the set
从片场回来后
I've always been at home alone
我一直一个人在家
Miss Hanlu is like this
韩露小姐是这样的
Where are you and your friends?
你和你的朋友在哪里？
may be in danger
可能有危险
So only you tell me his identity
所以只有你告诉我他的身份
The purpose of his coming to Shanghai
他来上海的目的
Where else can I find him?
我还能在哪里找到他？
Only then can I help you
只有这样我才能帮助你
I already said that
我已经说过了
No friends have come to see me
没有朋友来看我
I hope Miss Hanlu
希望韩露小姐
You can trust me as before
你可以像以前一样相信我
sorry
对不起
I'm really tired today
我今天真的很累
want to rest
想休息
Is there anything else you want?
你还有什么想要的吗？
Can you sign your name for me?
你能帮我签个名吗？
sure
当然
Thanks
谢谢
Where did you go wild?
你去哪儿野了？
Coming back so late
这么晚才回来
Since you can decide your own affairs
既然你自己的事情可以自己决定
don't listen to me
别听我的
Then where should I go?
那我该去哪里呢？
I don’t need to report to you, right?
我不需要向你汇报，对吧？
I am asking you
我在问你
you
你
go out
出去
where have you been
你去哪儿了
Why did you come back so late?
你怎么这么晚才回来？
get out of the way get out of the way
闪开 闪开
I want to sleep
我想睡觉了
I won't sleep in the house anymore
我不会再在屋子里睡觉了
I sleep on the sofa
我睡沙发
You went to find Hanlu
你去找韩璐了
nation in danger
国家处于危险之中
family disharmony
家庭不和睦
Only illusory idol stars
只有虚幻的偶像明星
Can bring me a little happiness
能给我带来一点点幸福
So shameless
太无耻了
No future
没有未来
tasteless
无味的
No shame or shame
没有羞耻或耻辱
If Zuo Shuangtao is really a lurker
如果左双涛真的是潜伏者
Every time I behave slightly abnormally
每当我表现稍有异常时
She must be given a reasonable explanation
必须给她一个合理的解释
But a hundred secrets and a sparse
但一百个秘密和一个稀疏的
There will always be a time when she sees a flaw
她总会有看到缺点的时候
Is it really the only way
这真的是唯一的方法吗
Abandoned the mission and evacuated?
放弃任务撤离？
Or is there any other way
或者还有其他办法吗
Let Guoguo leave voluntarily?
让果果主动离开？
Her hidden mission
她的隐藏使命
What exactly is it?
到底是什么？
I'm here today
我今天在这里
It's because I really don't know what to do
因为我真的不知道该怎么办
There is no one around me who tells the truth.
我周围没有人说真话。
the only mother you can trust
你唯一可以信任的母亲
Also in my teens
也在我十几岁的时候
He was killed by the Japanese
他被日本人杀了
the day after she died
她死后的第二天
her good sister
她的好姐妹
Just sold me
刚刚把我卖了
A landowner who is more than 30 years older than me is my concubine
比我大三十多岁的地主是我的小妾
I soon became pregnant with his child.
不久我就怀上了他的孩子。
I think this is good too
我觉得这个也不错
We can depend on each other as mother and son
我们可以像母子一样互相依靠
Live like this for the rest of your life
就这样度过余生
Smoothly
顺利
But he is doing business for himself
但他是为自己做生意
Forced me to abort the child
逼我打掉孩子
Call me his little daughter
叫我他的小女儿
Gave it to Luo Guanqun
Gave it to Luo Guanqun
I don't ask for anything else
我不求别的
I'm alone in this world
我独自一人在这个世界上
I just want to be here in Shanghai
我只想待在上海
Live a peaceful life
过着平静的生活
No matter who you are with
不管你和谁在一起
Miss Zuo
Miss Zuo
Please call me Mrs. Chen
请叫我陈小姐
in my heart
在我心里
You will always be just Miss Zuo
你永远只是左小姐
because I know
因为我知道
Your so-called wedding
你所谓的婚礼
Just to get the button
只是为了获得按钮
It's just a secret message method
这只是一个秘密消息方法
buttons
纽扣
here with me
在这陪着我
Mr. Yamashita
山下先生
What's going on here
这里发生了什么
Button's Secret Message
按钮的秘密消息
is double encrypted
是双重加密的
Even the Japanese secret service
就连日本特勤局
All at a loss
一切都茫然了
no one can decipher
无人能破译
Except I put it high
除非我把它放得很高
So you know who I am
所以你知道我是谁
From the day you discovered my secret transmitter
从你发现我的秘密传送器的那天起
I should have guessed
我应该猜到的
I simply can't accept it
我简直无法接受
I am as stupid as Chen Jiaping
我和陈家平一样傻
I was actually deceived by you
其实我是被你骗了
You are so self-righteous
你就是这么自以为是
was before
之前是
Still
仍然
therefore
所以
I also admire you more
我也更加佩服你
So is this how you express your admiration?
这就是你表达钦佩的方式吗？
I know
我知道
Now this way
现在这样
you will feel i am there
你会感觉到我就在那里
Blackmail you
敲诈你
but i have to do it
但我必须这么做
Only in this way
只有这样
Only then can we spend more time together
只有这样我们才能有更多的时间在一起
I don't want to miss you
我不想错过你
I can't miss you either
我也不能错过你
having said so much
说了这么多
Let’s talk about your conditions
说说你的条件吧
very simple
很简单
Divorced Chen Jiaping
离婚的陈家平
impossible
不可能的
why is it impossible
为什么不可能
Your marriage was a scam to begin with
你的婚姻从一开始就是一场骗局
You don't love him at all
你根本不爱他
if at a wedding
如果在婚礼上
You can get the contents of the secret message
即可获取密文内容
You abandoned him long ago and walked away
你早已抛弃他转身离去
Isn't it?
不是吗？
If I divorce Chen Jiaping
如果我和陈家平离婚
It will definitely arouse the suspicion of Zhao An and Luo Guanqun.
肯定会引起赵安和罗冠群的怀疑。
You don’t want me to fall into their hands, right?
你不想让我落入他们的手中吧？
you have a point
你有一定道理
but
但
Even if we don’t get divorced for the time being
就算暂时不离婚
we can still be together
我们仍然可以在一起
We can date secretly
我们可以秘密约会
How do you want to date
你想怎样约会
I want that
我要那个
slowly
慢慢地
step by step dating
一步步约会
I don't just want one
我不只想要一个
result
结果
What I want is the complete process
我想要的是完整的过程
from encounter
来自相遇
to understand
去理解
familiar with
熟悉
finally fall in love
终于坠入爱河
As long as you do what I say
只要你按我说的去做
I will give you what you want
我会给你你想要的
And you
你呢
You will definitely fall in love with me too
你一定也会爱上我的
But why should I believe it?
但我为什么要相信呢？
The thing is in your hand
东西在你手里
Tomorrow at 2pm
明天下午 2 点
Qinka Cafe on Jiafei Road
Qinka Cafe on Jiafei Road
here for me
在这里为我
It's a special place
这是一个特别的地方
I'll bring what you want
我会带你想要的东西
waiting for you there
在那里等你
Can't tell anyone about this
不能告诉任何人这件事
I told Lu Fangfang
I told Lu Fangfang
Why did you tell her?
你为什么告诉她？
Don't be angry
别生气
If I don't tell Lu Fangfang
如果我不告诉卢芳芳
how could I know
我怎么知道
Gao Fang has a crush on Zuo Shuangtao
Gao Fang has a crush on Zuo Shuangtao
Besides
除了
I just said I saw the two of them together
我只是说我看到他们两个在一起了
Tomorrow the two of them
明天他们两个
Another date at the coffee shop
咖啡店的另一次约会
Then I didn’t say anything.
然后我什么也没说。
did you hear
你听到了吗
What did Gao Fang use to blackmail Zuo Shuangtao?
What did Gao Fang use to blackmail Zuo Shuangtao?
On the ground at that time
当时在地上
A snake came out of nowhere
一条蛇不知从何而来
I was scared to death
我吓死了
So what did they say later?
那么他们后来怎么说呢？
I didn't hear it clearly
我没听清楚
maybe i know that thing
也许我知道那件事
what is
什么是
Lu Fangfang
Lu Fangfang
Which month's report are you looking for?
您要查找哪个月的报告？
What door should I close?
我应该关什么门？
Sit down and let me tell you something
坐下来让我告诉你一件事
sit
坐
What's the matter?
怎么了？
mysterious
神秘
Did you and your wife have a fight?
你和你老婆吵架了吗？
How did you know
你怎么知道
Let me tell you something
让我告诉你一件事
Don't blame me for talking too much
别怪我话太多
You say it
你说
This morning
今天早上
Mega Park
超级公园
your wife
你妻子
Are you dating Gao Fang?
你在和高芳交往吗？
what you saw
你看到了什么
what i heard
我听到了什么
Who did you listen to?
你听谁的？
Zhang Shuyun saw it with her own eyes
张淑云亲眼所见
no
不
What are my wife and Gao Fang doing together?
我老婆和高芳在一起做什么？
Anyway
反正
This Gao Fang held your wife’s hand
这位高放拉着你老婆的手
He even held my wife’s hand
他甚至握住了我妻子的手
She didn't resist either
她也没有反抗
If it weren't for the two of them,
如果不是他们两个
What else are you saying?
你还说什么？
I don't know that
我不知道
Zhang Shuyun told me this
张淑云告诉我的
I'm not trying to provoke you.
我并不是想激怒你。
I think so
我想是这样
These two peaches probably don’t like to play high
这两个桃子大概不喜欢玩high
I'm probably angry with you.
我可能对你很生气。
I advise you to coax her quickly.
我劝你赶紧哄她。
That's it for women
对于女人来说就是这样
Give her a step down
给她退一步
otherwise
否则
This fake show
这个假节目
Maybe it will be done
也许它会完成
play high
玩得高
Hello
你好
Section Chief Chen?
陈科长？
you are
你是
I'm from Yumo calligraphy and painting shop
我是玉墨字画店的
My surname is Lu
我姓卢
Boss Lu
卢老板
Hello
你好
Hello Hello
你好你好
The dragon tail inkstone you were anxious to ask for last time
上次你急着要的龙尾砚台
The store has arrived
专卖店已经到了
good
好的
I'll get it right away
我马上去拿
military rule
军事统治
Is this news accurate?
这个消息准确吗？
This is our comrade lurking in the army
这是我们潜伏在部队的战友
Information obtained
获得的信息
Accurate
准确的
Zuo Shuangtao was born in the 28th year of the Republic of China
左双涛 出生于民国28年
Joined the Jiangsu and Zhejiang Military Reunion Action Committee
加入江浙军联行动委员会
This is the introducer
这是介绍人
Liu Wuchang
Liu Wuchang
Her mission in Shanghai this time
她这次来上海的任务
Just to assassinate Yamashita Takeo
只为刺杀山下武夫
In fact, the military
事实上，军队
There is a secret letter
有一封秘密信
It fell into the hands of Yamashita Takeo
落入山下武夫手中
I should have thought of it a long time ago
我早就该想到的
Assassinations at train stations and weddings
火车站和婚礼上的暗杀
It's all Zuo Shuangtao's doing
都是左双涛干的
All kinds of doubts about her before
之前对她的种种质疑
Now there is an explanation
现在有一个解释
I thought I was using her to cover me
我以为我是在利用她来掩护我
In fact, she is also using me
其实她也在利用我
cover herself
遮盖自己
You don't have to blame yourself
你不必责怪自己
What we need to do now is to evacuate immediately
我们现在要做的就是立即撤离
I know
我知道
You are unwilling
你不愿意
But we have to take a long-term view
但我们必须要有长远的眼光
I want to leave for you
我想为你离开
Find a suitable reason
找一个合适的理由
There will be a chance in the future
以后还有机会
Only then can you return to the business
只有这样你才能重返职场
What reason are you looking for to leave?
你想找什么理由离开？
In order to make Luo Guanqun feel reasonable,
为了让罗冠群觉得有道理，
We also need to ensure that Guoguo is not suspected.
我们还要确保果果不被怀疑。
How about I choose this place?
我选这个地方怎么样？
Come
来
look
看
Do you think it's high-spirited?
你觉得是不是很有气势？
What would you use to blackmail Zuo Shuangtao?
你拿什么来敲诈左双涛？
Blackmail
勒索
Could it be pornographic photos?
会不会是色情照片？
Kimura said
木村说
After the assassination of Colonel Yamashita
山下大佐被刺杀后
The secret message he always carries
他始终携带的秘密信息
Missing
丢失的
They once suspected that Akun had taken it.
他们一度怀疑是阿昆拿走了。
Now it seems
现在看来
it's not true
这不是真的
Captain Zhao
Captain Zhao
what happened
发生了什么
assassinated
被暗杀
Then find someone to help you quickly.
然后尽快找人来帮助你。
I helped him stop the bleeding
我帮他止血
Go quickly
快去
Maybe Zuo Shuangtao took the secret letter
也许左双涛拿走了密信
but then
但是之后
An accident happened
发生了意外
Do you suspect that Gao Fang is blackmailing Zuo Shuangtao?
Do you suspect that Gao Fang is blackmailing Zuo Shuangtao?
It's a secret message from the military commander
这是来自军事指挥官的秘密消息
I originally wanted to listen to Kimura
本来想听木村的
Let’s not check this Zuoshuangtao anymore.
这个左双桃我们就不再查了。
But do you know
但你知道吗
I'm like a shark in the deep sea
我就像深海中的鲨鱼
Where do I swim?
我去哪里游泳？
I can smell the blood
我能闻到血的味道
And around this bloody smell
在这股血腥味的周围
The figure of Zuo Shuangtao is always indispensable
总是少不了左双涛的身影
can i be willing
我可以愿意吗
Remember?
记住？
repeat
重复
After meeting Gao Fang at Qinka Cafe
在琴卡咖啡馆遇见高放后
Confirm the secret message in hand first
先确认手上的密文
Then wait for an opportunity to poison the coffee
然后伺机给咖啡下毒
This medicine
这个药
Effective five minutes after taking
服用后五分钟有效
Symptoms similar to a heart attack
类似于心脏病发作的症状
You just have to wait for the poison to take hold
你只需要等待毒药发作
Just send him to the hospital
就送他去医院吧
This way even if someone sees you dating Gao Fang
这样就算别人看到你和高放约会
You won't be suspected of murder either
你也不会被怀疑谋杀
Why
为什么
what why
什么为什么
why all questions
为什么所有问题
It has to be solved by killing people
必须杀人才能解决
When I first suspected Chen Jiaping
当我第一次怀疑陈家平的时候
Want to kill Chen Jiaping
想要杀掉陈家平
The results of it
其结果
Killed A Kun
杀了阿坤
Now I know Gao Fang has a secret message in his hand
现在我知道高放手里有密信
And he did not hesitate to kill people and silence them
他毫不犹豫地杀人并让他们闭嘴
You want to disobey orders again, right?
你又想违抗命令是吗？
I will also go to the cafe today
今天我也去咖啡馆
In case of any accident
万一发生意外
I help in time
我及时帮忙
Aren't you just spying on me?
你这不是在偷看我吗？
Does it sound so nice to say it?
说起来有那么好听吗？
waiter
服务员
order
命令
elder brother
哥哥
They both came
他们俩都来了
Is what Gao Fang is holding in his hand a secret message?
高放手里拿着的东西是密信吗？
The truth will soon be revealed
真相很快就会揭晓
Hello sir
你好先生
Two lattes thanks
两杯拿铁谢谢
OK
好的
The latte in this shop is great
这家店的拿铁很棒
but
但
I haven't been here for a long time
我已经很久没来了
I don’t know if the taste has changed or not.
不知道味道有没有变。
Did you bring the secret message?
你带来了秘密信息吗？
Now you believe it
现在你相信了
elder brother
哥哥
Is that piece of paper a secret message?
那张纸是秘密信息吗？
I can't see clearly what's on it
我看不清上面有什么
but i think
但我觉得
yes
是的
Do you want to arrest someone?
你想逮捕某人吗？
No hurries
不着急
Can't run
无法运行
Let's see what they do behind the scenes
让我们看看他们在幕后做了什么
It hasn't changed at all
完全没有改变
your coffee sir
你的咖啡先生
Thanks
谢谢
It seems you have many stories with this cafe
看来你和这家咖啡馆有很多故事
my first love
我的初恋
She especially likes the latte here
她特别喜欢这里的拿铁
She and I often come together
我和她经常在一起
but
但
That was three years ago
那是三年前
you love her very much
你非常爱她
I'm willing to die for her
我愿意为她去死
That you
那个你
Why are we not together now?
为什么我们现在不在一起？
she is dead
她死了
I'm willing to die for her
我愿意为她去死
But what I didn't expect was
但没想到的是
She actually died because of me
她其实是因为我而死
It was my fault
是我的错
During the Battle of Songhu
淞沪之战期间
I used the bug I developed myself
我用的是我自己开发的bug
Eavesdropping on Japanese military intelligence
窃听日本军事情报
I learned that they would launch an air attack on Shanghai in three days.
我得知他们三天后将对上海发动空袭。
I first fell in love with their family
我首先爱上了他们的家人
We were obviously preparing to evacuate that night.
那天晚上我们显然正准备撤离。
But because she firmly believed
但因为她坚信
Believe my deciphering
相信我的破译
Delayed evacuation plan
延迟疏散计划
But that night
但那天晚上
The Japanese army launched an air raid on Shanghai
日军对上海发动空袭
I fell in love with their family for the first time
我第一次爱上了他们的家人
I killed her
我杀了她
Then you should hate the Japanese
那你应该讨厌日本人
Why do you still have to do things for them?
为什么还要为他们做事呢？
I didn't do anything for the Japanese
我没有为日本人做任何事
I just want to learn the most advanced deciphering technology
我只是想学习最先进的破译技术
you like me
你喜欢我
Is it because I look a lot like her?
是因为我长得很像她吗？
yes
是的
You are very similar
你们很相似
because of my family
因为我的家人
I used to be a relatively silent person
我曾经是一个比较沉默的人
But after I met her
但当我遇见她之后
she told me
她告诉我
Treat your life happily
对待你的生活幸福
and bring happiness
并带来幸福
pass it on to people around you
传递给你周围的人
I will never let the mistake happen a second time
我永远不会让错误发生第二次
I will definitely protect you
我一定会保护你的
This is not love for me
这不是对我的爱
It's self-salvation
这是自我救赎
this is Love
这就是爱
I know better than you
我比你更了解
sorry
对不起
I'm going to the bathroom
我要去卫生间
elder brother
哥哥
Arrest or not?
逮捕还是不逮捕？
what are we waiting for
我们还在等什么
You said that if Gao Fang really threatened Zuo Shuangtao?
你说如果高放真的威胁左双涛呢？
Will Zuo Shuangtao be captured obediently?
左双涛会乖乖被抓吗？
If it's our style
如果这是我们的风格
They will definitely kill people and silence them.
他们肯定会杀人并让他们闭嘴。
So don't rush
所以别着急
There might be a big surprise later
稍后可能会有大惊喜
This medicine
这个药
Effective five minutes after taking
服用后五分钟有效
Symptoms similar to a heart attack
类似于心脏病发作的症状
to be honest
说实话
I don't really like their latte
我不太喜欢他们的拿铁咖啡
I feel a little bitter
我感觉有点苦涩
or
或者
I'll also add a piece of sugar for you
我也给你加一块糖
Did you see it just now?
你刚才看到了吗？
What is Zuo Shuangtao holding in his hand?
左双涛手里拿着的是什么？
I saw
我看见
It seems like it should be a candy bar
看起来应该是棒棒糖
Except for candy bars
除了棒棒糖
what else
还有什么
besides
除了
Drink quickly
快点喝
It's all cold
一切都冷了
Look
看
I don't like their latte
我不喜欢他们的拿铁咖啡
So my first love with you
所以我对你的初恋
are two completely different people
是两个完全不同的人
I know there is a Cantonese sweet shop nearby
我知道附近有一家粤式甜品店
Very delicious
非常美味
In fact, today I want to eat pear stewed with rock sugar.
其实今天我想吃冰糖炖梨。
sorry
对不起
I want to stay a little longer
我想多呆一会儿
Strange
奇怪的
Why is there no movement?
为什么没有动静？
elder brother
哥哥
It seems that Zuo Shuangtao
看来左双涛
There was no act of resistance.
没有任何反抗行为。
Be prepared to arrest people
准备好逮捕人
If five minutes have passed
如果五分钟过去了
There is still no poisonous effect from high-level radioactivity
目前尚无高水平放射性的毒害作用
Liu Wuchang will definitely do it himself
刘无常一定会亲自去做
It's still hard to escape death even if you play high
就算玩得很high也难逃一死
You can only take Gao Fang out of the cafe first
你只能先带高放走出咖啡馆
Taking advantage of Liu Wuchang's hesitation
趁刘无常犹豫之际
Only by playing high can you have a chance to escape.
只有玩得高，才有机会逃脱。
play high
玩得高
If you really want to start a relationship with me
如果你真的想和我建立关系
You shouldn't keep us immersed in
你不应该让我们沉浸在
In the memories of you and your first love
在你和初恋的回忆里
you're right
你说得对
waiter
服务员
Pay the bill
支付账单
elder brother
哥哥
they are leaving
他们要离开
Arrests
逮捕
Miss Zuo
Miss Zuo
wait for me a while
等我一会儿
play high
玩得高
move
移动
good
好的